HasanMalikresume - 20199-2.pdf

Hasan M Malik

contact number : 0303-2091785

Email address: malik059@umn.edu

Profile/skills

- · Highly skilled in Microsoft Office and Google Suite.
- · Highly proficient writing, editing and proof reading skills.
- · Direct the planning and execution of university events.
- · Experience in working with university database systems.
- · Exceptional critical thinking and analytical skills.
- Excellent communication, presentation and Interpersonal skills.
- High level administrative and time-management skills.
- Proficient statistical, mathematical, and computer skills.
- Experience in collecting, compiling and processing statistical/business data.

EDUCATION

 University of Minnesota, Morris - Bachelors (Major: Economics, Minor: Statistics) -2013-2017

EXPERIENCE

University of Minnesota, Twin Cities - Office of the Registrar Executive Office and Administrative Specialist (Aug 2017 - Aug 2018)

- Serve as the team lead for the Imaging unit in regards to managing day-to-day activities of the student workers.
- Participate in project prioritization, strategic planning, and business process improvements for the Imaging unit and the Office of the Registrar.
- Responsible for the oversight of the day-to-day operations of the Imaging unit.
- Managing important/confidential documents in database systems.
- Ensure that best practices and academic records integrity are upheld and documented
- Track and analyze statistics to determine needs and enhancements in order to ensure service levels are maintained.
- Support the Office of the Registrar as an expert in Duplicate ID resolution.
- Planning and managing departmental budget.
- Handling of departmental mail.

Hasan M Malik

My Contact

malik059@umn.edu



+92 303 2091785



Karachi, Pakistan

Hard Skill

- · Administrative Skills
- Operating database systems
- · Financial management and budgeting
- Project Management
- · Data Analysis
- Web Development (HTML5, CSS and Javascript)

Soft Skill

- · Customer Service
- Decision making
- Leadership and Team Management
- Multi-tasking
- Adaptability
- Communication and Interpersonal skills

Education Background

University of Minnesota, Morris Bachelors in Economics, Minor: Statistics Completed in 2017

About Me

An experienced administrative professional with years of extensive experience in project coordination, handling confidential information, delivering top-notch customer service, and formulating strategies to accomplish organizational objectives. Adept at implementing process improvements in various administrative functions, including policy and procedure planning.

Professional Experience

Cafe Qayam | Sole Proprietor/Executive Manager

March 2022 - Present

- Leading and managing all restaurant employees in a fast-paced working environment
- Implementing innovative marketing strategies to increase business sales
- · Managing all financial and operational aspects of the business
- · Hiring and training a diverse team of staff members

Kaiser Restaurant | Senior Manager

September 2018 - February 2022

- Administered operations on a daily basis and ensured protocol was followed by staff
- Reviewed financial transactions and allocated restaurant budget more efficiently
- Managed food inventory, ensuring stock was sufficient at all times
- Monitored food preparation to ensure 100% customer satisfaction

University of Minnesota, Twin Cities - Office of the Registrar | Executive Operations and Administrative **Specialist**

Aug 2017 - July 2018

- Served as the team lead for the Imaging unit in regards to managing day-to-day
- activities of the student workers
- Processed enrollment requests for non-degree graduate and undergraduate students.
- Participated in project prioritization, strategic planning, and business process improvements for the Imaging unit and the Office of the Registrar.

Languages

Fluent in English, Urdu and Hindi

- Supervised daily operations of the imaging unit, ensuring it's efficient and effective functioning
- Managed important/confidential documents in database systems.
- Ensured that best practices and academic records integrity are upheld and documented
- Tracked and analysed statistics to determine needs and enhancements in order to ensure service levels are maintained
- Supported the Office of the Registrar as an expert in Duplicate ID resolution
- Planned and managed departmental budget

University of Minnesota, Morris - One Stop Student Services | Customer Relations Representative

August 2016 - December 2016

- Worked with applications such as Salesforce and People soft to manage student information
- Handled all student inquiries via phone, email and in person
- Record Keeping of One Stop counsellors schedule and availability